<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
	                <rss version="2.0"> 
	                    <channel> 
	                        <title>Grosskreutzs Kavallerie. War, War makes money.</title> 
	                        <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php</link> 
	                        <description>The Grosskreutzs Kavallerie was formed in late 3027. During that time Albert Grosskreutz got enough from political maneuverings of LCAF and it's ineffectiveness. That leaded to founding of his own private military organization. Backed by Grosskreutz's family inheritance and connections GKK was born and ready for action in January 3028. That time The Kavellerie had already almost two companies of 'Mechs, platoon of Pattons and company of infantry. 
Oberst Grosskreutz has been careful when choosing contracts. It's not unheard that he chooses to wait month or two for good contracts if non is found fast. While this has resulted some months without employer it also helped to keep GKK away from more risky contracts. The Kavallerie has done various contracts for many employers, including DCMS, FWLM, AFFS and ComStar. Primarily focusing on Garrison and raiding type of contracts. 
In mid-30s the Kavallerie is growing to regimental size. When completed GKK would have 'Mech Battalion, Combat Vehicle Battalion, highly mobile Infantry Battalion and support elements. Oberst Grosskreutz wants to have flexible yet heavy hitting force that can complete various tasks.
Dragoon Rating: B
Officers   Oberst Grosskreutz is unusual commander as he doesn't have traditional military background often assosiated to Mercenary Command leader. He has background in LCAF's Strategies and Tactics Division, where he worked as expert on warfare and economics fields. During 3020s Grosskreutz gathered core of GKK's officers from LCAF and various mercenary contacts. Late 3030's GKK send their most promising young officer candidates to various Military Academies across InnerSphere.
Tactics  GKK emphasizes mission-type tactics. Sub-Commander are free to reach mission goals as they see best. This gives GKK high-degree of flexibility to adapt any situation needed. Different styles of combat are often seen depending of commanding officer in field, thus making GKK unpredictable adversary. attleMechs are primary combat units that Combat Vehicle and Infantry supports. GKK favors heavily armored and relatively fast 'Mech and other vehicle designs.
Support  The Kavallerie fields enough DropShips to transport whole command. They also have Invader and Merchant class JumpShips to transport their DropShips. Mid-30s enlargement project is going to force the Kavallerie to seek more DropShip capacity if they plan to maintain fully independent transport capability. The Kavallerie support staff is half manned if compared to standard house regular unit. They can maintain Kavallerie's equipment but shortages in manpower makes repair periods after battles very hectic.</description> 
	                        <language>english</language>  <item>
	                <title>Overall look for Prospectivity Zero</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=76&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>Major locations of Warfer's Mining on planet Prospectivity Zero
Port Prospectivity Zero
Population ~5500
"Capital" of Prospectivity Zero.
Commonly just Port.

-Administrative HQs
WMO Warfer's Mining Operations' main administrative center in planet. 
WSF Warfer's Security Forces' HQ.
GKK Grosskreutzs Kavellerie's HQ.

-DropShip Port 
Capability for 10 DropShips. (Five Reserved for GKK)
GKK's logistical and maintenance center.

-Radars Installation
Used to survey local airspace and near objects in space under WSF control.

-Airfield
Many civilian (mainly WMO) transport aicrafts.
3 WMO's Surveillance aircrafts.
4 WSF's Fighter aircafts.
2 GKK's Fighter aircafts.
4 GKK's Helicopters.

-Hospital
Only hospital in planet.

-Major storage Hub
Large warehouse complex used to store inbound and outbound goods.

-Small harbor

Cove
Population ~3000
-Ore Refining, logistical and maintenance area serving all northern mining sites.
-Small Airfield capacble of serving VTOL and SVTOL aircrafts.
-Small Harbor.

Hills
Population ~2000
Residential area serving Gamma, Delta and Epsilon Mining Sites.

Harbor
Population ~500
Small residential area serving Beta Mining Site.

North and South Gates
Combined Population ~150
Twin ports located in strait at narrowest point of the Lake. 

-Small ports for ferry traffic.
Used as main route between northern mining areas and Port of the Lake. Strait is only five kilometers long at it's narrowest point. Route is served by two large ferries. One of them is usually in reserve or under repairs while other serves traffic.</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Urbanized Suns</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=75&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Opportunists(Kintaro, Hunchback, Hatchetman and Enforcer)

vs

AFFS
Medium Lance (Marauder, Rifleman, Enforecer, Wolfhound).



Terrain: Suburban area / City Edge
Mission: Engage enemy and inflict as much damage as possible without own losses.
 


AFFS Lance took positions just inside town using civilian buildings as makeshift covers. Opportunists started to close AFFS's positions using small forests as cover. Theodoros Stian lance leader of Opportunists kept his lance in thigh formation during mad dash to town limit. AFFS concentrated their fire to Chin Ping's Hunchback scoring number of hits. Meanwhile AFFS wolfhound flanked Opportunists trying to get behind their line. 
 
When Opportunist reached town's edge AFFS 'Mech retreated inside forcing battle to be fought in urban environment. Stian ordered his lance to concentrate their fire to Marauder as it was most probably AFFS lance's command Mech. At the initial barrage Marauder took several hits to it's right torso destroying it and also damaging engine. AFFS reprised by concentrating to Hatchetman and damaging it slightly. 
 
Stunned by initial strike AFFS lance contracted to hedgehog defense excluding lone wolfhound that was lurking in opportunists rear. Drago headed to engage Wolfhound. As almost all AFFS 'Mechs were behind building only Stian's Kintaro was able to find firing solution but all shots missed or hit to buildings. Luckily Marauder also shoot buildings making them very likely to collapse. 
 
AFFS wolfhound didn't want to play with Drago's Enforcer and headed back to town and straight to huge warehouse. Marauder also headed to nearby factory to seek cover. Keeping mission goals in mind Stian ordered his lance back to town edge while keeping AFFS 'Mech pinned. Only Rifleman was in position to be shot and shoot back. Couple of shots went back and forth netting almost all of Rifleman's left torso and Hunchbacks head took hit from large laser. 
 
Marauder and Rifleman badly damaged GKK started to orderly retreat. AFFS 'Mechs also retreated deeper into town. Battle seemed to be almost over.
 


Battle was fought with "blind individual initiative" </description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Situation Update for Operation Franc's Inhuman Guile </title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=74&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>From: GKK operational HQ
To: GKK BattleMech Company Commanders
Subject: Situation Update for Operation Franc's Inhuman Guile
Date: 1st August 3039

We made planetfall with 7th and 8th Ghost's at July 19. After four day battle in Solus City 3rd FedCom garrison units were fleeing to join the 5th Davion Guard RCT in Origian Military Reservation. Our part of urban fighting was heavy and cost us serveral 'Mechs downed. After enemy was driven from city we managed to engage and destroy several rearguard units. 

Unfortunately 3rd FedCom's Assault elements were able to mount suprise attack against 7th Ghosts and we weren't able to counter that in time. DCMS operational command ordered our 1st 'Mech Company against breach point. That went south at the start because Scholae Palatinae weren't close enough and two lances against superior enemy (in numbers and weight) in good defensive terrain was doomed. It costed us practically half of our Assault 'Mechs and Dust Devils Lance as combat unit. Enemy was even able to evacuate their fallen 'Mechs and our Battlemaster.

After July's fighting enemy's 5th Davion Guard RCT and 3rd FedCom RCT are currently retreating, as 7th and 8th Ghost's pushed AFFS's from Origian Military Reservation. Ghost's are currently engaging 5th's rear guard elements. We are currently positioned to cover 8th Ghosts Right Flank. 


Our Strenth:
We are down to 24 'Mechs from original 32 'Mechs.
Platoon worth of Schacal Hover Tank's are out of action but repairable.
Small number of infantry casualities.

DMCS's estimated strenth:
7th Ghost Regiment: Down to ~80% 
8th Ghost Regiment: Down to ~65% 

AFFS's estimated strenth:
5th Davion Guard RCT: Down to ~65% 
3rd FedCom RCT: Down to ~50% 


Current BattleMech Strenth

Fevered Molers: All 4 'Mechs in fighting condition

Scholae Palatinae: All 4 'Mechs in fighting condition
-Battle Damage: Stephan Sigfried's Banshee BNC-3E out of action, needs replacement parts
+Transfer: Richard Friedman with WHM-6D

Dust Devils: 0 'Mechs in fighting condition
-Battle Damage: Viktor Brand's VTR-9B out of action, needs replacement parts
-Transfer: Richard Friedman with WHM-6D
-Battle Damage: Wolfgang Junker's (MIA) GHR-5H out of action, needs replacement parts
-Battle Damage: Edward Diegos's BLR-1G Damaged and lost to enemy 

Firestorm: 2 'Mechs in fighting condition
-Battle Damage: Emil Kluge's ARC-2W out of action, needs replacement parts
-Battle Damage: Leanddro Maetje's BJ-1 out of action, needs replacement parts
  
Opportunists: All 4 'Mechs in fighting condition

Delta 4: All 4 'Mechs in fighting condition

Sprinters: All 4 'Mechs in fighting condition

Pathfinders: 2 'Mechs in fighting condition
-Battle Damage: Michael Schultz's HER-1A out of action, needs replacement parts
-Battle Damage: Hitomi Kei's LCT-1V out of action, needs replacement parts

</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Convoy Raiding</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=70&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Fevered Molers &amp; Delta 4

vs

AFFS
Heavy Lance
(Highlander, Black Knight, Orion and Lynx)

Terrain: Open plains

GKK was ordered to raid enemy supply convoys near frontlines. Soon intelligence located convoy of four trucks with lance of heavy 'Mechs as escort. Fevered Molers and Delta 4 engaged enemy 'Mechs. 

With 2 to 1 numerical advantage and more manouverable 'Mechs Manwin ordered his 'Mechs to keep moving, use terrain and keep good distance. This allowed GKK's 'Mechs to soften slower and heavier AFFS 'Mechs while they tried to move. Black Knight and Orion took many hits while only couple connected Delta 4's 'Mechs. 

Once AFFS 'Mechs were some 300 or 400 meters away from GKK's line Manwin ordered Fevered Molers and Delta 4 to swarm enemy Lance. GKK's main focus was Black Knight that was heavily damaged and eventually lost all it's weapons save the head mounted Small Laser. 

Meanwhile Orion too took bucketload of hit's and fell to the ground with exploding consequences. Now GKK's 'Mechs too started to show battledamage but Manwin was able to rotate more heavily damaged 'Mechs to safe from heaviest battle. Black Knight stripped bare and Orion destroyed GKK's 'Mechs concentrated their fire to Highlander and it too was grippled after ammunition explosion. Lynx's 'Mechwarrior used this time to make his escape. 

All enemy trucks were disable or destroyed, depriving AFFS forces for much need supplies. Three enemy 'Mechs were more or less salvagable. Only GKK casuality was Vulcan's Right hand.


Battle was fought with "blind individual initiative"</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Gone bad</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=69&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Fevered Molers &amp; Dust Devils

vs

AFFS
Assault and Heavy Lance

Terrain hilly woodlands

AFFS made promicing breakthrough attemt and GKK's 'Mech lances in area were ordered to counter attack. Odds were strongly stacked against this operation because AFFS got good defensive terrain and more 'Mechs in area, but regardless of these factors assault was ordered. GKK's lances made their way towards enemy defencive line and started probing attacks. Fevered Molers and Dust Devils engaged two heavier AFFS lances. AFFS Awesome was first to fall when Richard Friedmann shot it's engine. Regardless of this early success tide soon turned against GKK's forces. Soon GKK's 'Mechs very heavily mauled and were forced to retraet. Rearguard Battlemaster and Grasshopper fell for enemy fire. Edward Diego was lucky enough to escape but Wolfgang Junker was captured.


Battle was fought with "blind individual initiative"</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Rear guards engaged</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=67&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Pathfinders Lance (Cicada, Hermes, Hermes II and Locust) and 2nd Strike Platoon (4x Schakal A1)
vs
AFFS
Dervish, Griffin, Phoenixhawk and two medium Hovercafts

Result:
Battle was between GKK's Scouting force and AFFS's rearguard element. AFFS fought reatreating battle through patchwork forrest towards small lake. GKK's unit's  got numerical advantage 8 to 5, but got much lighter 'Mechs. Also this was first real battle to GKK's Schakal Hovertanks. 

AFFS forces eliminated, only minor damage to GKK 'Mechs and Vehicles. Hermes' had popped off and Locust lots it's hand completely. One of the Schakal's took bad hit to drive systems, but was able to got home. Hitomi Key with her Locust was able to kill AFFS's Dervish. All it took was three consecutive hits to Dervish's center torso location from backside. One AFFS's Hovercraft tried to use rive to get away, but that retreat ended rather deep.

(This was first battle where we tested "blind individual initiative".) </description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>HQ Assaulted</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=68&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK &amp; 6th Ghosts
GKK's Firestorm Lance with Ghosts Assault Lance
vs
AFFS
Assault Lances, assorted HQ Vehicles and medium Hovercraft Platoon.

Result:
AFFS HQ destroyed and only one AFFS mech survived and retreated area.

Ghost's Commande's 'Mech destroyed but rest of lance took only light damage. Severe damage to all GKK's 'Mechs. Firestorm lance is effectively out of combat for long time.</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Breaking the Line (retry)</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=64&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Scholae Palatinae &amp; Firestorm
vs
AFFS
Heavy &amp; Medium Lance

Result:
Battle was gain fought in Solus City. GKK advanced AFFS defensive positions trying to inflict as much damage as possible before inevitable hand to hand combat near crucial intersection. After regrouping GKK charged waekened enemy positions using Banshee and Modified Battlemaster as spearhead. Enemy was overran and half of enemy 'Mechs was destroyd and rest fled from area. GKK was able to capture and hold important road link and denie enemy to counter attack Ghosts' ongoing break through.</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Breaking the Line</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=63&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>GKK
Fevered Molers &amp; Dust Devils
vs
AFFS
Assault &amp; Heavy Lance

Result:
Battle was fought in Solus City heavily urbanized area. AFFS choosed to care little of civilian infrastructure and damaged many bildings while trying to get better positions. Finally both sides choose to disengage as battle was going to severely cripple both. Brand's Viktor took damage to engine and gyro and was barely able to get back and many GKK's 'Mechs had lost considerable amount of armor. AFFS's lances took at least same amount of damage and two of their heviest machs were almost immobile. 

</description> 
	            </item><item>
	                <title>Contract Franc's Inhuman Guile</title> 
	                <link>http://koti.kapsi.fi/~darkkis/bt/gkk/index.php?action=news&amp;log=72&amp;first=0</link> 
	                <description>From: CO Grosskreutz
To: GKK's Officers
Subject: Contract/Operation Franc's Inhuman Guile
Date: 17th May 3039

As our contract in Junction is ended and recent Davion/Lyran aggression against Combine borders, DCMS is contracted us to complement their counter attack forces targeting system Sadalbari. We are to join two DCMS's regiments and retake planet from AFFS forces. Planet is currently held by 5th Davion Guard RCT and 3rd FedCom RCT. DCMS still has 2nd Shin Legion in planet fighting delay until reinforcements arrive. Sadalbari is important to DC because it's crucial supply route to system Proserpina which is probably one of AFFS main target in this district.

This assault will be one of the toughest jobs we ever had. While it's not expected that we play any major role in this attack it's still highly possible that casualties and losses will rise. To counter that risk contract rights are extremely favorable to us. This is good opportunity to gain valuable experience and make good C-Bills.

We are to leave Junction immediately and head to staging area to join main DCMS force designated to recapture Sadalbari.</description> 
	            </item></channel>
	                </rss>